

DECISION MAHOFA

IT Ops

- **J** 0782389377
- Bluffhill, Harare, 263 Harare
- ## June 7, 1997
- ېت Male
- hofdee.aithub.ic
- in linkedin.com/in/decision-mahofa-456829206

SKILLS

Coder (Vanilla JS, React.js, Laravel, Node.js, Git, Azure)

VSAT Installations

3СХ

Zabbix Monitoring

Kubernetes

LANGUAGES

English

Shona

Setswana

French

HOBBIES

- Camping
- Gaming
- Fishing

PROFILE

A resourceful and goal oriented professional with sound experience in the IT industry, with a demonstrated history of working in the logistics, mining and government systems industry. Skilled in IT Strategy, Cisco Meraki platform, Security and Systems administration. I am committed to achieving and exceeding demanding targets and business objectives while remaining focused on providing an exceptional standard of service.

EDUCATION

Bsc. Computer Science

Aug 2016 - May 2020

NUST, Bulawayo

Degree Classification - 2.1

EMPLOYMENT

IT Intern

Aug 2018 - Nov 2019

Bikita Minerals Pvt. (Ltd), Masvingo

- Day to day network monitoring and optimization.
- Hardware replacements, server and domain administration.
- Expedited software subscription payments and upgrades like Belina and Sage Pastel.
- Automated backups and redundancy.
- Improved and expedited the acquisition of computers, officeware, consumables and software purchases.
- Collaborated on a successful project to upgrade mine network coverage by adding a base station on a nearby hill Key Achievements:
- Designed and installed network system on a newly sited 2-floor building.

<u>I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruitment for</u> the position to which I am applying.

- Coding
- Tree Planting
- Sporting [Basketball, Cricket]

QUALITIES

- Growth mindset
- Self motivated and hardworking
- Time management

IT Ops

May 2021 - Present

1010 Technologies, Harare

- 2nd line IT support
- Network configuration, maintenance and monitoring
- System and User acceptance testing
- 3CX Administration
- Windows and Linux Operating System Ops and Configs
- Datacenter support
- Client apps and business solutions support [eGorvenance]
- Product management and Go Live support
- Frontend App Development (Javascript, React.js)

CERTIFICATES

AZ-104 Microsoft Azure Adminstrator

AZ-305 Microsoft Azure Solutions Architect

DP-100 - Microsoft Azure Data Scientist Associate

PROJECTS

- appleplug.store
- welodge.co.zw
- Printer Fault Prediction App

REFERENCES

Leejay Tavares

1010 Technologies, Harare

+263772234469, leejayt@1010tech.io

Jonah Chindomu

1010 Technologies, Harare

263772422889, jonahc@1010tech.io